bagheeraboutique.com 2017-03-22

# Site Conditions - BagheeraBoutique

**A) PRIVACY POLICY (D.lgs. 196/2003)**  
 **A.1) Interested parties**  
The website Bagheeraboutique.com is owned by the company Bagheera Italia srl ("Bagheera”), managing and organising the products on sale.  
BAGHEERA is registered at the Registro delle Imprese di Roma, CF/P.IVA 09790281001, seated in Via Filacciano 5 – 00188 Rome Italy.

BAGHEERA is the holder of your personal data according to the D. Lgs. N. 196, June 30, 2003 (Personal Data Protection Code). The above mentioned legislation regulates the protection of persons and other parties with reference to personal data. Personal data are treated in accordance with the current legislation.  
 **  
A.2) Nature of the bestowal** Data bestowal has a relevant nature, as it deals with information the knowledge of which is suitable for the hereafter indicated purposes. Furthermore, BAGHEERA informs you that failure or wrong communication of compulsory data may prevent the Holder from ensuring the congruity of the treatment and may also lead to a suspension of BAGHEERA responsibility with reference to the consequences of such untruthfulness. **

A.3) Data treatment purposes

** Personal data are collected and handled by BAGHEERA for purposes connected with the use and related services offered by the web-site and with the products purchase via Bagheeraboutique. Com, as follows:  

  * we collect personal data with reference to the subscribing process that is necessary to allow access to the reserved areas of Bagheeraboutique.com and the forwarding of the news via e-mail, when requested.;
  * With reference to customer care, we collect personal data in order to provide all the necessary information about Bagheeraboutique.com services and products purchasing.
  * With regard to the purchasing process at Bagheeraboutique.com we collect data through the order form.
  * We collect data in order to provide technical assistance concerning internet navigation, browser compatibility and Bagheeraboutique.com loading and display

Personal data are in most cases electronically treated. In some cases, (for example to avoid fraud) the information may be handled in paper format.   
Personal data are retained in order to enable their indentification within the period of time that is strictly necessary to achieve the specified purposes, in accordance to the current legislation.   
Please notify any modification in your personal data at [customercare@Bagheeraboutique.com](mailto:%20customercare@Bagheeraboutique.com).  
We do not disclose personal information to third parties for illegal purposes or without your express consent. Data will be disclosed to third parties if this is required for completing your transaction with us (for instance, the Banca sella requires such data for payment operations). Furthermore, data will be forwarded to the Police or to the Judicial Authority, according to the current legislation and upon formal request (for example within anti-fraud services of Bagheeraboutique.com).  
BAGHEERA handles your data for direct marketing purposes with your express consent only.   
In some cases BAGHEERA might be treating personal data of third parties involved in the purchasing process: this occurs, for instance, when the subscriber buys an item to be dispatched to a friend, that is when the paying subject differs from the product receiver. This also happens when the subscriber intends to indicate the services (or a specific offer) provided by Bagheeraboutique.com to a friend .  
In such cases, the customer is obliged to obtain the express consent from the person to whom data are referred and to inform him about the present Privacy Policy. The customer is the sole responsible for the disclosure of data and information of third parties without their express consent, or for illegal purposes. We inform you that the consent of such third parties is not necessary when their data are communicated to BAGHEERA for completing the contract with the company .  
 **  
A4) Data treatment modalities** Data treatment is carried out through paper or electronic format or any other means present and future, with particular reference to:  

  * Entrustment of elaboration operations to third parties
  * Computer handling
  * Manual treatment (paper archives)

Personal data handling occurs in accordance with the Privacy Code (art. 11, 31 and following) and by the adoption, in compliance with the disciplinary measures included in the Annex B, of the minimum security measures regulated in the Privacy Code, Art. 35.   
By acceptance, the interested party expresses the consent to data treatment according to the above mentioned conditions, including disclosure to third parties. Thus, BAGHEERA acquires the faculty of using data, also for commercial purposes and with reference to data banks in which information might be included, or for any other use.  
 **  
A5) Communication**  
Data are stored at the Handler’s offices, and will be communicated to the competent subjects for the implementation of the necessary operations, in order to guarantee a proper management of the business relationship and the safeguard of the user’s rights.  
Data are handled by staff , collaborators, and by the service company of BAGHEERA.   
Data might be disclosed without restrictions- especially in a exemplifying way- to third parties 

Dhl/Bartolini for the handling of data necessary to carry out dispatching activities, including restitution of goods purchased at Bagheeraboutique.com  

  * Brgcom s.r.l., handling data with reference to BAGHEERA’s server management and maintainance
  * Banca Sella

Personal data will also be disclosed for purposes indicated at point A3) to external collaborators, or to all those subjects to whom data communication is necessary for the proper accomplishment of aims mentioned at point A3)  
 **  
A.6) Disclosure**  
Collected data shall be communicated/disclosed without restriction to third parties if the Handler believes it to be necessary.  
 **  
A.7) Handler**  
BAGHEERA is the Handler of the user’s personal data and decides in conditions of full autonomy on the treatment modalities, security profile included.  
 **  
A.8) Rights of the user**  
The user is allowed at any time to exercise the rights indicated in D.Lgs. 196/2003, art. 7, that is he has the right to erase, modify, update and integrate his personal data. By sending an e-mail to [customercare@bagheeraboutique.com](mailto:%20customercare@Bagheeraboutique.com), you will receive an updated list of the subjects responsible for data handling.  
 **  
A.9) Modifications and updating of Privacy Policy of Bagheeraboutique.com**  
BAGHEERA is allowed to modify or simply update, totally or partially, the Privacy Policy at Bagheeraboutique.com, also considering possible modifications occurring in legislation regulating the present matter and safeguard your rights. Modifications and updates of the Privacy Policy will be notified to the users at the home page of the web-site, and will be operative and binding beginning from the day of their publication at Bagheeraboutique.com Please visit regularly the home page, so that you can read the most recent and up-to-date version of the Privacy Policy at Bagheeraboutique.com.  
 **  
A.10) Operative Effectiveness**  
The above mentioned rules shall be applied to all present and future tasks –verbal agreement included - entrusted to BAGHEERA.  
 **Copying of art. 13 D. Lgs. 30 giugno 2003, n. 196**

**Information on cookies**

Websites use smart and useful techniques to make them easier to use and more interesting for individual visitors. One of the best known techniques is to use cookies. Cookies can be used by website owners or third parties, for example advertisers, that communicate through the website being visited.

Cookies are small text files that the website stores in users’ computers. The information contained in cookies can also be used to track browsing of different websites that use the same cookie.

Cookies are classified according to duration and the site that set them.

Users must be informed about the cookies that our website uses and about the purposes for which they are used. There are three purposes: to ensure your privacy, make the site easy to use and optimise the development of our websites. Below is a more detailed explanation of the cookies used in our websites and their purpose.

**Use of cookies by this website**

This website uses cookies to collect statistical data on visitors and to record information on your preferences as you browse websites. Our purpose in using cookies is to improve the experience our site offers to visitors.

**Cookies and their functionality**

Different cookies are used for the various purposes.   
Below is a list of the most commonly used types of cookie and the purposes for which they are used.

**Session cookies**    
Session cookies are filed temporarily in the computer’s memory while you are browsing a site, for example, to track the language chosen. Session cookies remain stored in the computer for a short period of time. They are deleted as soon as the user closes the web browser.

**Permanent or tracking cookies**    
Permanent cookies save a file on the computer for a long period of time. This type of cookie has an expiry date. Permanent cookies enable websites to remember information and settings for users’ subsequent visits, making browsing quicker and more convenient as, for example, they no longer need to log in.   
On the expiry date, cookies are automatically deleted when you first access the website that created them.

**First-party cookies**    
These cookies are set by the websites themselves (with a domain that matches the domain in the browser address bar) and can be read only from these sites. They are commonly used to file information such as preferences to be used during subsequent visits to the site.

**Third-party cookies**    
These cookies are set by domains other than that indicated in the browser address bar, meaning by organisations other than the website owners.   
Cookies used, for example, to collect information for advertising purposes or to customise content, as well as to process web statistics, may be third-party cookies.   
Third-party cookies can be used to survey users’ browsing habits more fully and are considered more sensitive from an integrity point of view. This is why most web browsers allow settings to be changed so that these cookies are not accepted.

Below is a list of services used on this website that set third-party cookies:

**Google Analytics (Google)**    
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google") which uses cookies to collect users’ personal data which is sent to, and stored on, Google servers in the United States. Google uses this information to track and examine your use of the website, compile reports on website activity for the website operators and provide other services related to website activity and Internet use. Google does not associate users’ IP addresses with any other data that it possesses. If you refuse to use cookies, by selecting the appropriate setting on your browser, you may not be able to use all that website’s functionality.

**Social Widgets/Buttons**    
Services that enable users to interact with social networks from within other websites.

**Facebook social buttons/widgets (Facebook)**    
Service managed by Facebook Inc., a company that has signed up to the Safe Harbor Privacy Policy Framework, guaranteeing personal data processing in line with European safety standards. The service allows users to interact with the social network through this website. If a user clicks on the button/widget, Facebook acquires data about that user’s visit to the site. Facebook does not share any information or data in its possession with the site or the data controller. For more information on Facebook Inc.’s use of personal data, please see the following link: www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php

**Twitter social buttons/widgets (Twitter)**    
Service managed by Twitter, a company that has signed up to the Safe Harbor Privacy Policy Framework, guaranteeing personal data processing in line with European safety standards. The service allows users to interact with the social network through this website. If a user clicks on the button/widget, Twitter acquires data about that user’s visit to the site. Twitter does not share any information or data in its possession with the site or the data controller. For more information on Twitter’s use of personal data, please see the following link: twitter.com/privacy

**Cookie management**

As cookies are normal text files, they can be accessed using most text editors or word processing programs. To open them you just need to click on them. Below is a list of links that explain how to view cookies within the various browsers. If your browser is not listed, refer to the information on cookies provided by the browser. If you use a mobile phone, see the manual to find more information.

Firefox   
https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer

Chrome  
https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647&topic=14666&ctx=topic

Internet Explorer   
http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies

Safari   
http://support.apple.com/kb/PH17191?viewlocale=it_IT

**Deactivating/activating or deleting cookies**

Cookies can be limited or blocked depending on the browser settings.

If you would like websites not to store any cookies on your computer, set your browser so that it receives a notification before any cookie is filed. Alternatively, you can set your browser so that it rejects all cookies or only third-party cookies. You can also delete all cookies already present in the system. It is important to stress that settings must be edited separately in each browser and computer used.

If you block the storage of cookies, this website cannot guarantee that it will work properly. Some site functions may be unavailable and you may not be able to view certain websites. In addition, blocking cookies does not stop advertisements being displayed. They will simply not be customised according to your interests and may be displayed more frequently.

Each browser uses a different procedure for editing settings. If necessary, use the browser guide function to find the correct procedure.

To deactivate cookies on a mobile phone, see the manual to find more information.

More detailed information on cookies on the Internet can be found at http://www.aboutcookies.org/

**Other cookies/unexpected cookies**

Because of the way the Internet and websites work, we are not always able to control the cookies that are stored by third parties through our website. This is especially the case when webpages contain so-called incorporated elements such as text, documents, pictures or video clips that are filed elsewhere but are viewed on or through our website.   
So if you find a cookie on the website that is not attributable to one of the third-party services listed, please let us know. Alternatively, you can contact the third parties concerned directly and ask for information on the cookies that they send, their purpose, their duration and how they guarantee users’ privacy.
